// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "The software life cycle can be said to consist of a series of phases. The classical model is referred to as the waterfall model. Which phase defined as â€œThe concept is explored and refined, and the clients requirements are elicited?",
    answer: "Requirements",
    options: [
      "Requirements",
      "Specification",
      "Design",
      "Implementation"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "In the maintenance phase the product must be tested against previous test cases. This is known as _________ testing.",
    answer: "Regression",
    options: [
      "Unit",
      "Integration",
      "Regression",
      "Module"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The relationship between a derived class (or subclass) and base class is referred to as",
    answer: "Inheritance",
    options: [
      "Association",
      "Inheritance",
      "Polymorphism",
      "Instantiation"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What are the major activities of the spiral model of software engineering? ",
    answer: "Planning, Risk Analysis, Engineering, Customer Evaluation",
    options: [
      "Defining, Prototyping, Testing, Delivery",
      "Planning, Risk Analysis, Engineering, Customer Evaluation",
      "Requirements",
      "Quick Design, Build Prototype, Evaluate Prototype, Refine Prototype"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: " A process view in software engineering would consider which of the following " ,
    answer: "Functionality",
    options: [
      "Product performance",
      "Staffing",
      "Functionality",
      "Reliability"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: " What is the essence of software engineering?" ,
    answer: "Managing Complexity, Managing Personnel Resources, Managing Time and Money and Producing Useful Products",
    options: [
      "Requirements Definition, Design Representation, Knowledge Capture and Quality Factors",
      "Maintaining Configurations, Organizing Teams, Channeling Creativity and Planning Resource Use",
      "Time/Space Tradeoffs, Optimizing Process, Minimizing Communication and Problem Decomposition",
      "Managing Complexity, Managing Personnel Resources, Managing Time and Money and Producing Useful Products"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: " Which of the following projects would be a good one for adopting the prototyping paradigm for software development?" ,
    answer: " Algebra Tutor",
    options: [
      "Accounting System",
      "Spreadsheet",
      "Automobile Cruise Control",
      " Algebra Tutor"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is the first step in the software development lifecycle?" ,
    answer: "Preliminary Investigation and Analysis",
    options: [
      "System Design",
      "Coding",
      "System Testing",
      "Preliminary Investigation and Analysis"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What does the study of an existing system refer to? " ,
    answer: "System Analysis",
    options: [
      "Details of DFD",
      "Feasibility Study",
      "System Analysis",
      "System Planning"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: " What does RAD stand for?" ,
    answer: "	Rapid Application Development",
    options: [
      "	Rapid Application Document",
      "Rapid Application Development",
      "Relative Application Development",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  
  

  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];